<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<application>
  <id type="desktop">Thunar.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <summary>File Browser</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Thunar is a file browser specifically designed for the Xfce Desktop, but also can serve as an alternate file browser for other Desktop environments. It has a simple, clean two-pane design for browsing all your files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">ثونار متصفح ملفات مصمم خصيصا لسطح مكتب Xfce. لكن يمكن استعماله كتصفح ملفات بديل في بيئات مكتب أخرى. يتميز ثونار بتصميم بسيط يمكنك من تصفح جميع ملفاتك.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Thunar ye un restolador de ficheros diseñáu específicamente pal escritoriu Xfce, pero tamién pue sirvir como restolador de ficheros alternativu pa otros entornos d'escritoriu. Tien un simple y llimpiu diseñu a dos cares pa restolar tolos tos ficheros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Thunar е файлов мениджър, разработен специално за десктопа на Xfce, но може да се използва, като алтернативен файлов мениджър и в други графични среди. Той е с изчистен двупанелен дизайн за да управлявате лесно вашите файлове.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Thunar és un navegador de fitxers que està dissenyat especialment per a l'escriptori Xfce, però també pot servir com a navegador de fitxers per a altres escriptoris. Té un disseny simple, de dos plafons, per navegar per tots els vostres fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Thunar je správce souborů specificky navržený pro prostředí Xfce, ale může také sloužit jako alternativní aplikace pro procházení souborů v jiných desktopových prostředích. Má jednoduchý čistý dvoupanelový design pro procházení všech Vašich souborů.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Thunar er en filbrowser, der er særligt designet til Xfce-skrivebordet, men kan også tjene til en alternativ filbrowser for andre skrivebordsmiljøer. Den har et simpelt, klart design med to paneler, der lader dig gennemse dine filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Thunar ist eine Dateiverwaltung speziell für den Xfce-Schreibtisch entwickelt, kann aber auch als alternativer Dateinavigator für andere Arbeitsumgebungen benutzt werden. Er hat eine einfache, aufgeräumte Zweifensteransicht zum Durchsuchen aller Ihrer Dateien.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Thunar είναι ένας διαχειριστής αρχείων ειδικά σχεδιασμένος για το περιβάλλον εργασίας Xfce, αλλά μπορεί να χρησιμοποιηθεί ως εναλλακτικός διαχειριστής αρχείων για άλλα περιβάλλοντα εργασίας. Έχει μια απλή, καθαρή σχεδίαση 2 πινάκων για περιήγηση των αρχείων σας.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_AU">Thunar is a file browser specifically designed for the Xfce Desktop, but also can serve as an alternate file browser for other Desktop environments. It has a simple, clean two-pane design for browsing all your files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Thunar is a file browser specifically designed for the Xfce Desktop, but also can serve as an alternate file browser for other Desktop environments. It has a simple, clean two-pane design for browsing all your files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Thunar es un gestor de archivos diseñado específicamente para el escritorio Xfce, pero puede usarse también en otros entornos de escritorio. Su interfaz de doble panel es sencilla y clara.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Thunar on tiedostoselain, joka on suunniteltu erityisesti Xfce-työpöydälle, mutta jota voi käyttää vaihtoehtoisena tiedostoselaimena myös muilla työpöytäjärjestelmillä. Se käyttää yksinkertaista kaksiruutuista muotoilua kaikkien tiedostojesi selaamiseen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Thunar est un gestionnaire de fichiers conçu spécifiquement pour le bureau Xfce, mais peut aussi servir comme gestionnaire de fichiers alternatif pour d’autres environnements de bureau. Il dispose d’une interface à deux panneaux simple et épurée pour parcourir tous vos fichiers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Thunar é un xestor de ficheiros deseñado especificamente para o Escritorio XFCE, o cal tamén pode servir como explorador de ficheiros alternativo para outros ambientes de traballo. Este ten un deseño simple con dous paneis para ver todos os seus ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">‏Thunar הינו סייר קבצים אשר תוכנן בקפידה עבור שולחן עבודה Xfce, אך גם יכול לשרת בתור דפדפן קבצים חלופי עבור סביבות שולחן עבודה אחרות. יש לו עיצוב פשוט, נקי בעל שתי חלוניות לסיור בכל הקבצים שלך.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Thunar je upravitelj datotekama posebno dizajniran za Xfce radno okruženje, ali jednako se može koristiti kao alternativni upravitelj datotekama u drugim radnim okruženjima. Posjeduje jednostavan dvokrilni dizajn za sve vaše datoteke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Thunar kifejezetten az Xfce asztali környezethez tervezett fájlkezelő, de más asztali környezeteket is kiszolgál, alternatív fájlkezelőként. Egyszerű, tiszta, két táblás felülete van, minden fájl böngészéséhez.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Thunar adalah peramban berkas yang dirancang khusus untuk Destop Xfce, tetapi juga dapat berfungsi sebagai peramban berkas alternatif untuk lingkungan Destop lainnya. Thunar memiliki desain yang sederhana, desain dua-pane bersih untuk meramban semua berkas Anda.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Thunar er skráastjóri sem sérstaklega er hannaður fyrir XFCE-skjáborðið, en se hægt er að nota sem aukaskjástjóra í öðrum skjáborðsumhverfum. Thunar byggist á einfaldri og stílhreinni tveggja-spjalda hönnun til að vafra um skrár og möppur.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Thunar è un browser dei file pensato per l'ambiente Xfce, ma può essere utilizzato come browser di file alternativo in altri ambienti desktop. Ha un design semplice a due riquadri adatto per sfogliare tutti i propri file.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">Thunar は Xfce デスクトップ環境用に開発されたファイルブラウザーであり、他のデスクトップ環境でも使用できます。シンプルでクリーンな 2 ペインデザインで設計されており、すべてのファイルを閲覧できます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Thunar - бұл Xfce жұмыс үстелі үшін арнайы жасалған файлдық басқарушы қолданбасы, сонымен қатар, оны басқа да жұмыс үстел орталарында қосымша ретінде қолдануға болады. Оның қарапайым әрі жеңіл екі панельді интерфейсі файлдарды шолу үшін арналған.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Thunar는 Xfce 데스크탑을 위해 특별히 설계된 파일 브라우저이지만, 다른 데스크탑 환경에서 대체 파일 브라우저로 사용가능합니다. 모든 파일을 브라우징 할 수있는 간단한 두개의 패널 디자인으로 구성되어있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Thunar yra, specialiai Xfce Darbalaukiui sukurta, failų tvarkytuvė, tačiau ji gali tarnauti kaip alternatyvi failų tvarkytuvė ir kitose Darbalaukio aplinkose. Ji turi paprastą, tvarkingą dviejų polangių dizainą jūsų visų failų naršymui.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Thunar ialah pelayar fail yang direka khusus untuk Desktop Xfce, tetapi juga bertindak sebagai pelayar fail alternatif untuk persekitaran Desktop lain. Ia mempunyai rekabentuk ringkas, dengan dua-anak-tetingkap yang kemas unntuk pelayaran semua fail anda.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Thunar er en filutforsker spesifikt utviklet for Xfce-skrivebordet, men kan også fungere som en alternativ filutforsker for andre skrivebordsmiljø, Den har et simpelt, rent to-felts designuttrykk for filene dine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Thunar is een bestandbeheerder die specifiek is ontworpen voor de Xfce-werkomgeving, maar hij kan ook dienen als een alternatieve bestandbeheerder in andere werkomgevingen. Hij heeft een eenvoudig, helder dubbelpaneelontwerp om al uw bestanden te kunnen doorbladeren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Thunar er ein filutforskar spesielt utvikla for Xfce-skrivebordet, men han kan òg fungera som ein alternativ utforskar for andre skrivebordsmiljø. Thunar gir deg ei enkel, rein to-panelsutforming for å bla gjennom filene dine. </p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Thunar es un gestionari de fichièrs concebut especificament pel burèu Xfce, mas pòt tanben servir coma gestionari de fichièrs alternatiu per d’autres environaments de burèu. Dispausa d’una interfàcia de dos panèls simpla e epurada per percórrer totes vòstres fichièrs.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Thunar to przeglądarka plików zaprojektowana specjalnie dla środowiska graficznego Xfce, ale może służyć także jako alternatywna przeglądarka plików w innych środowiskach. Posiada proste, czytelne dwupanelowe wzornictwo dla przeglądania wszystkich plików.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Thunar é um gestor de ficheiros especificamente desenhado para o ambiente Xfce, mas também poder servir como gestor de ficheiros para outros ambientes gráficos. Tem um simples e limpo design para explorar todos os ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Thunar é um navegador de arquivos especificamente desenhado para o Desktop Xfce, mas também pode servir como navegador de arquivos alternativo para outros ambientes de Desktop. Thunar apresenta um simples e limpo design de dois painéis para a navegação de todos os seus arquivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Thunar este un manager de fișiere creat special pentru mediul desktop Xfce, dar care poate fi folosit ca un manager de fișiere alternativ și în alte medii desktop. Are un design clasic și minimal ce vă ușurează gestionarea tuturor fișierelor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Thunar — файловый менеджер специально для рабочего окружения Xfce, но может использоваться как альтернативный в других рабочих окружениях. Имеет простой опрятный двухпанельный вид для просмотра всех ваших файлов.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Thunar je správca súborov navrhnutý špeciálne pre Xfce Desktop, ale možno ho používať aj ako alternatívneho správcu súborov v iných pracovných prostrediach. Ponúka prostý, plne dvoj-panelový vzhľad na prechádzanie všetkých súborov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Тунар је управник датотека нарочито осмишљен за Иксфце радно окружење, али може и да служи као замена за управника датотека другим радним окружењима. Има једноставни и чисти склоп са две површи за управљање датотекама.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Thunar är en filhanterare speciellt utformad för Xfce-skrivbordet, men den kan också användas som alternativ filhanterare i andra skrivbordsmiljöer. Den har en enkel tvåpanelsdesign för att bläddra bland alla dina filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">Thunar เป็นโปรแกรมท่องดูแฟ้มซึ่งออกแบบมาสำหรับเดสก์ท็อป Xfce โดยเฉพาะ แต่ก็สามารถทำงานเป็นโปรแกรมท่องดูแฟ้มทางเลือกสำหรับเดสก์ท็อปอื่นได้ด้วย การออกแบบจะเรียบง่าย ทำงานสองช่องแบบสะอาดตา เพื่อท่องดูแฟ้มทั้งหมดของคุณ</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Thunar özel olarak Xfce Masaüstü için dosya tarayıcısı olarak geliştirilmiş olsa da diğer Masaüstü ortamları için de alternatif dosya tarayıcısı olarak kullanılabilir. Dosyalarınızı taramak için iki parçalı basit ve temiz bir tasarımı vardır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Thunar - це переглядач структури файлів, розроблений спеціально для оболонки Xfce, однак також може слугувати як альтернативний переглядач фалів для інших середовищ робочого столу. Він простий, має двопанельний дизайн для показу файлів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Thunar 是一个专门针对 Xfce 桌面环境设计的文件浏览器，但它也能作为其他桌面环境的替代文件浏览器。它有一个简洁的双栏式设计让您浏览所有的文件。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">Thunar 是一個為 Xfce 桌面設計的檔案瀏覽器，但也可以作為其他桌面環境的替代檔案瀏覽器。它有一個簡易且簡潔的兩欄式設計讓您瀏覽您所有的檔案。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://xfce.org/projects</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.xfce.org/describecomponents.cgi?product=Thunar</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.xfce.org/xfce/thunar/start</url>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">http://docs.xfce.org/_media/xfce/thunar/file-manager-window.png</screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <updatecontact>xfce4-dev@xfce.org</updatecontact>
</application>